[ED]
[car whirring]
Hey, I was just...
[car clunks]
Ready, go!
Yes!
Um, here we go.
Okay, okay.
You want to come in now?
Imiss Uright already.
Nowhere yet
Beyond the Heart
Yes, sir.
All of it.
No way.
Close your eyes.
Close your eyes first.
Close them.
Yes, sir.
Open them.
Yes.
Everything.
No reckless infinite
Statistics
You can come back to me
Rehearsal for the last show in Osaka is over!
I hope you all enjoyed the show.
We worked until the very last minute to make sure everyone had a good time.
Wait a minute, isn't it a little warm?
Wait a minute, it's warm here.
It's too humid.
Can you let me through to the office?
Why?
I brought this. I don't know what to do with it.
I'm not supposed to answer too many questions.
By the way, what do adults like?
Do you have a favorite food?
I'm not supposed to answer that many questions.
Favorite food?
Can I tell you?
Between you and me, do you have a favorite food?
Juice.
I like melon.
To your last point.
It's private.
Private.
Soy mayo, please.
Yes, sir.
Six.
Yes, thank you.
Thank you very much.
I have one sauced mayo.
Yes, sir.
If you hurt your neck...
It hurts like hell.
Like this.
It's bad, isn't it?
The top one...
It's different.
It's so hard!
You're like...
They're all different.
I have a different kind of neck pain.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Yay.
I wish my dad could have some.
Here you go, sir. Sauce mayo.
Be careful
Hoku hoku hoku hoku
Noodles are delicious, aren't they?
Yes, they are.
Kira gave it to me.
What's that?
Tamene.
She bought it for me?
Yeah.
This one...
So cute!
Ta-da!
Takoyaki (octopus dumplings)
Bon appétit!
Rico and I made eye contact.
They are looking at me.
Bon appétit!
Delicious!
How long have you had this? Seriously.
What? How long have you had this?
I'm just so focused.
You know, when I was watching the video.
Yui's interrupting me.
I thought she was interrupting me a lot.
I was about to get mad at her and told her to stop.
Why don't you show your face?
I want takoyaki!I want to eat takoyaki!
I want to eat takoyaki!
Bon appétit!
Give her an oan.
What?
For the audience?
Oh, my God.
Ready, go!
What are you eating?
Look at that. It's too much egg.
It smells so good.
What's wrong?
What is it?
Shrimp dumplings.
Shrimp dumplings? What's that?
Try it.
Everyone, I found it!
Yes, sir.
What are you eating?
Shumai!
They're eating shumai.
Someone picked at the shumai.
And then...
Hey, look.
Wave to them.
That's great!
You're good!
Enjoy your meal.
There's two of them.
What are you doing?
Oh, yeah, they've got this cute little guy here.
That made me laugh.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Excuse me.
What?
I think he had a little accident at the end. I saw him crash.
That's right.
What do you eat?
What's that?
Looks delicious.
Saul cake.
You two eat so close together?
Looks delicious!
Good.
We're at the salon.
What happened to you earlier?
I worked hard.
It's nice.
Is it good?
What are you eating?
Mr. Doshima.
I'm eating, Mr. Michijima.
Oh, so that's what you mean.
LOL.
Then, I'll have some, too.
It looks like you're relaxing your body, doesn't it?
Actually, it's not just that.
You're also relaxing your mind.
Actually, after the trainer loosened me up.
I'm going to be able to move today because I've been relaxed by the trainer.
I can move today because I've been relaxed by the trainer.
I said, "I'm so happy!
I'm so happy, I'm so happy.
Thank you very much.
Good night.
We've got four services today.
What a cute daddy's boy.
Yes, OK.
I wanted to drop you off on the second day.
I've got an earpiece that will be more on the first day.
Everyone votes accordingly.
I'm going to go change now.
We're almost ready to go live.
One hour ago.
I'm going to get dressed.
I can hear the sound.
Backstage passageway.
Backstage.
There's a... you know what I mean?
You can see the back.
I don't know if I'm allowed to show you this much.
But it's so formidable.
Oh, sure.
I always fix my makeup here.
This is where I always look at the monitor.
Head bottles.
I wonder if we have a guest.
Here are the stairs.
It looks like this.
Now, it's an emergency meeting.
We have an emergency meeting every day about MC.
We have call-and-response, what to say, and who should be in charge of who,
I'm going to be facilitating the meeting today,
I will be facilitating the meeting today, but each MC has been meeting with various people to make it happen.
This is an emergency meeting. Excuse me.
Can you make it?
I can do it.
You can do it, right?
You'll give away our secret.
That's so hard to believe.That's really hard to find.
Is it stopped?
It's stopped.
Is it average length?
Can you turn it down?
It's okay.
Breathe.
Breathe so that your belly and back expand.
Finally.
We had the fall last week in a blink of an eye.
We've come so far together amazingly well, and
I think we can do it with confidence and
We have a lot of activities to do after this.
We have our 6th album coming up.
I'm sure there will be a lot of activities in the future.
I think this is the start of the road to the future.
Today is not the last day.
I hope it will be a big step for us.
Let's do our best to entertain everyone at today's show.
Let's do our best!
Let's make Birdies happy!
Seino
Always be strong with curry
Take the sake like the cherry blossoms
just trust lines
sake sake sake sake
Sakura Taka 46
Mankai!
sakura-taka46 manka-ai
Thank you for your hard work
Now
What a surprise!
We're on the air now!
It's the show!
I'll do my best
Let's go!
I'm going!
No?
Can't go?
I want to go, I want to go, I want to go!
Yes, yes, yes!
I'll do my best!
Marino
Ms. Pattee?
Yes, yes, yes!
I'll do my best
I'll do my best, I'll do my best, I'll do my best
Okay, let's go.
Let's go
Yes, kagiwa nagare
Thank you very much for coming to Sakurazaka 46 Third Tour 2023 today!
As previously announced, regarding the guidelines for this performance.
As previously announced, the guideline for this performance is the circuit of cheering in loud voices and cheering with the wearing of masks as a proscribed rule.
We will continue to follow the guidelines for this performance.
The show will begin shortly.
The show is about to begin!
It's time for Jeonju Raku! You all can speak louder, can't you?
Now we, JK Cormi and Marie Lima, are going to have a battle of the voices.
JK lick it up, Se-no Osaka!
Teresama!
KONNAGI
I love Buddy's!
Let's get this show on the road!
Not so much.
Studying...
I'm off.
Thank you for watching.
Aroma
r
I still don't know all the correct answers.
Still a little bit of calm down in case of overnoon
How to dance with rich developmental qualities
I want to be loved I want to be loved
I want to be loved I want to be loved I want to be loved
The sound of the stage
Let's all get excited!
Good evening. This is BLACKPINK.
Hello.
Ending
We would like to send you love from us.
We love you, Ollies!
We love you!
Farewell to you, seh, shakin!
We want to reach all the female staff in all the spheres today, so
All of you, please speak up!
Everyone!
Let's get excited about the magic game!
Yeah!
Let's make the magic happen!
Thank you for your hard work.
We'll be on our way shortly. Everyone will be going shortly.
Okay, let's go.
Please come on in.
Here we go.
Thank you for watching.
I'll take that for you.
Yoo-hoo!
The live show is over.
That went by so fast, didn't it, Seishaku?It all happened so fast, didn't it?
It's our home town in Kansai.
Kansai, our hometown.
Oh, no. Hyogo.
Hyogo, right?
Oh, Kansai.
Deer.
Kansai.
If I ask you to watch Sakura Meets, will you watch it?
Look at Sakura Meets!
Watch it!
Good night.